I wrote two down for one so this can get
confusing and so I'm going to do the
next one and switch them around this is
going to be 71 and that is a law app I
don't think I've talked about it and
stuff in one of the ones I've had an
idea of but we clearly silly lawyers but
anything that a computer can do just by
reading the law and us helping it learn
meaning like once but maybe it's a
person that tells it the rule that like
if you speed you get this parking ticket
or if you are parked here here the ways
you can have a defense does this apply
to discipline you having an app that
locks you through the when you don't
need a lawyer so it's not that you need
them to sign something or notarize
something but you need to just know the
law having the log be accessible so that
everyday people don't need to pay
hundreds of dollars to access the law
and you're still going to need to pay
the expertise to when you then need the
lawyer when you're being sued when
you're suing someone when you're under
arrest there's lots of ways we will
still need lawyers but to be able to get
basic law questions ourselves in every
country because that's important too
when you're in another country like here
are the things when you travel and we
have them it's easy to compare databases
of like parking you know gets you your
hands cut off I don't know that's
clearly not happening in any country but
it's like by its certain violations that
are no big deal in your country you can
get you in jail or more severe
punishments that aren't even legal in
your country so a law app is Apple
number 71